[{"answer": "I know, I know.  Hello", "docId": "212toasb.htm.txt", "asentId": 3, "question": "Hi my friend", "qsentId": 2}, {"answer": "Oh, wow", "docId": "212toasb.htm.txt", "asentId": 5, "question": "Oh, I would love to have kids. . . you're, you're the, you're, me play the songs that I will write for them", "qsentId": 4}, {"answer": "my friend knows. Do you have any idea who else knows", "docId": "212toasb.htm.txt", "asentId": 7, "question": "Hmm, my friend knows huh? Ahh, hello Mr. my friend, enigma of the trees, upsid", "qsentId": 6}, {"answer": "Your monkey found a new career, in the entertainment field. That's all I know", "docId": "212toasb.htm.txt", "asentId": 9, "question": "So, what is this information worth to you, my friend", "qsentId": 8}, {"answer": "Ahhhh", "docId": "212toasb.htm.txt", "asentId": 11, "question": "Uh, yes, yes it is", "qsentId": 10}, {"answer": "You don't think I'm cute", "docId": "212toasb.htm.txt", "asentId": 13, "question": "You can tell her I think her friend is cute", "qsentId": 12}, {"answer": "Um, so listen, how many times am I gonna have to touch you on the arm before you ask me on a date", "docId": "212toasb.htm.txt", "asentId": 15, "question": "I'll be there, and who knows, if things go well, maybe this time I'll get to see your underwear", "qsentId": 14}, {"answer": "Oh, OK, I don't eat meat", "docId": "212toasb.htm.txt", "asentId": 17, "question": "Well you know, you juist, you eat them and you can tell", "qsentId": 16}, {"answer": "But um, here's an idea, have you ever worn women's underwear", "docId": "212toasb.htm.txt", "asentId": 19, "question": "Well I was thinking it would be um, kind of sexy if you wore mine tonight, at dinner", "qsentId": 18}, {"answer": "That is the most ridiculous", "docId": "212toasb.htm.txt", "asentId": 21, "question": "I did not sell you out", "qsentId": 20}, {"answer": "OK, well, you wouldn't let me finish and I was ju", "docId": "212toasb.htm.txt", "asentId": 23, "question": "Ow, you stop flicking", "qsentId": 22}, {"answer": "Because I went to an all boys high school and my friend is making up for it", "docId": "212toasb.htm.txt", "asentId": 25, "question": "Right now, right here. Don't ya think we're in kind of a public plaaaa  They do have the shrimp", "qsentId": 24}, {"answer": "This is for the fourth grade", "docId": "212toasb.htm.txt", "asentId": 27, "question": "Whaddo I mean. Whaddya mean, whaddo I mean? I mean underpants, mister, that's what I mean", "qsentId": 26}, {"answer": "Huh? Where, whaddya mean", "docId": "212toasb.htm.txt", "asentId": 29, "question": "What, what's what you mean", "qsentId": 28}, {"answer": "My skirt, you lifted, kids laughing. I was Susie Underpants 'till I was 18", "docId": "212toasb.htm.txt", "asentId": 31, "question": "Well um, why don't you call me in 20 years and tell me if you're still upset about this.", "qsentId": 30}, {"answer": "my friend", "docId": "212toasb.htm.txt", "asentId": 33, "question": "Oh, no no no, she took off with my clothes", "qsentId": 32}, {"answer": "I was not trying them out, my friend asked me to wear them", "docId": "212toasb.htm.txt", "asentId": 35, "question": "No. I'm not letting you or anybody else see, ever", "qsentId": 34}, {"answer": "Alright, one of you give me your underpants", "docId": "212toasb.htm.txt", "asentId": 37, "question": "How can you not be wearing any underwear", "qsentId": 36}]